So now that we know about these powerful features,
-: والآن بعد أن علمنا بهذه الميزات القوية
an obvious question is, why would we use that?
، فإن السؤال الواضح هو ، لماذا نستخدم ذلك؟
Why is that helpful?
لماذا هذا مفيد؟
Well, it is useful in situations like this,
حسنًا ، إنه مفيد في مثل هذه المواقف ، حيث
where we know we want to have
نعلم أننا نريد الحصول على
a certain set of functionalities.
مجموعة معينة من الوظائف.
Let's say a greet method, and we want to ensure
لنفترض طريقة الترحيب ، ونريد التأكد
that a clause has such a greet method,
من أن الفقرة لها طريقة الترحيب هذه ، وقد
and another clause has it maybe as well,
تحتوي جملة أخرى عليها أيضًا ، حسنًا
well, then, we can implement an interface
، إذن ، يمكننا تنفيذ واجهة
which forces the existence of this method.
تفرض وجود هذه الطريقة.
Then we can easily share functionality amongst clauses,
بعد ذلك يمكننا بسهولة مشاركة الوظائف بين
and every clause has to add its own implementation,
الجمل ، ويجب أن تضيف كل فقرة التنفيذ الخاص بها
the exact code that should execute
، الكود الدقيق الذي يجب تنفيذه
when the method is called,
عند استدعاء الطريقة
but we enforce a certain structure
، لكننا نفرض بنية معينة بمساعدة
with the help of interfaces.
الواجهات.
This can be useful if we don't have other parts of our code
يمكن أن يكون هذا مفيدًا إذا لم يكن لدينا أجزاء أخرى من الكود
which rely on that structure.
الخاص بنا والتي تعتمد على هذه البنية.
Here, we set user1 to be of type Greetable,
هنا ، قمنا بتعيين user1 ليكون من النوع Greetable
and with that we say we don't care what's inside user,
، وبهذا نقول إننا لا نهتم بما بداخل المستخدم ، ولكن ما
but what has to be in there is a greet method,
يجب أن يكون هناك طريقة ترحيب ، ونعلم أنه
and we know that it has to be in there
يجب أن يكون هناك لأنه مهما كان
because whatever we store in user1 has to be greetable.
يجب أن يكون التخزين في user1 قابلاً للترحيب.
That allows us to write truly powerful and flexible code
يسمح لنا ذلك بكتابة رمز قوي ومرن حقًا حيث لا يتعين علينا
where we don't have to know everything about a object,
معرفة كل شيء عن كائن ، أو كل شيء عن جملة
or everything about a clause,
، لكننا نعلم فقط أن كل ما أحصل
but we just know whatever I'm getting here in user1
عليه هنا في user1 يجب أن يكون لديه طريقة ترحيب.
We don't care whether Person has anything else,
نحن لا نهتم بما إذا كان لدى الشخص أي شيء آخر
here we're interested in greet,
، فنحن مهتمون هنا بالترحيب ،
hence we sent us to Greetable,
ومن ثم أرسلنا إلى Greetable
and therefore we can't store anything in user1
، وبالتالي لا يمكننا تخزين أي شيء في user1 والذي
which would not have a greet method,
لن يكون له طريقة ترحيب ، لأن الترحيب
because Greetable forces whatever you base on it
يفرض أيًا كان قاعدتك عليه أن يكون لديك مثل هذا الأسلوب الترحيب.